<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Participants on Open Security Summit</title><link>/oss2020/participant/</link><description>Recent content in Participants on Open Security Summit</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/oss2020/participant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/oss2020/participant/_template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/oss2020/participant/_template/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Dinis Cruz</title><link>/oss2020/participant/dinis-cruz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/oss2020/participant/dinis-cruz/</guid><description>Dinis Cruz is the CISO of the Photobox Group and is focused on creating an team and environment where security is an enabler and accelerator for the business, while securing and protecting the digital assets from existing threats.
Dinis is very active in open source communities like OWASP, where he was a board member. He is currently part of the leadership team behind the Open Security Summit 2019, which brings together the Security community in an open and collaborative environment to work on hard security challenges we face today.</description></item><item><title>Felipe Zipitria</title><link>/oss2020/participant/felipe-zipitria/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/oss2020/participant/felipe-zipitria/</guid><description>Felipe is a Msc. in Computer Security from University of the Republic (Uruguay). He has been working as a DevOps / System Administrator for 20 years, and as a Security Consultant for 10+ years. He has been teaching Computer Security Fundamentals to pregraduate students and Web Application Security for postgraduates at the local public University.</description></item><item><title>Jemma Davis</title><link>/oss2020/participant/jemma-davis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/oss2020/participant/jemma-davis/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Tash Norris</title><link>/oss2020/participant/tash-norris/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/oss2020/participant/tash-norris/</guid><description>Tash Norris is the Senior Cloud Security and Threat Modeler at Photobox Group.</description></item></channel></rss>