<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DevSecOps on Open Security Summit</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/ciso/</link><description>Recent content in DevSecOps on Open Security Summit</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/ciso/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cyber Risk Modeling</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/ciso/cyber-risk-modeling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/ciso/cyber-risk-modeling/</guid><description>Phil brings his extensive experience to a discussion on modelling (general) risk and comparing security risk modelling maturity to other markets (finance, insurance, medical..). This also involves attribution of $ value to risk and how security teams can talk the language of the business
Current Security Risk Management is Broken There is a lot of complexity and uncertainty in cyber risk. Current practice tends to hide uncertainty and present certainty.</description></item><item><title>How does a CISO add value to a business?</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/ciso/ciso-add-value-to-a-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/ciso/ciso-add-value-to-a-business/</guid><description> Topics to cover: Can we add value to the business through more closely aligned strategies? What are the new skills needed? How do we find the balance between technical competence and management skills? What are the challenges and opportunities associated with elevating the CISO into a business critical partner?</description></item><item><title>Supply Chain assurance</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/ciso/supply-chain-assurance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/ciso/supply-chain-assurance/</guid><description>WHY It’s not efficient for every outfit to ask their own Qs that are very similar. But CISOs are reluctant to trust BitSight/RiskLedger/other 3rd party compliance snapshots. So, how do we do dynamic assurance in a collective manner?</description></item><item><title>Third Party Due Diligence</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/ciso/third-party-due-diligence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/ciso/third-party-due-diligence/</guid><description>Why Every company has their own third party due diligence methods. Mostly a mix of questionnaires, open source investigations, sometimes onsite assessments. This is not efficient in today&amp;rsquo;s world as poor vendors are forced to spend 100s of hours each year filling in questionniares with same or similar questions over and over again.
What I believe we should have a restricted opensource platform where the members would agree on a framework and scoring system for third party due diigence from cyber perspective.</description></item></channel></rss>