<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wardley Maps on Open Security Summit</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/</link><description>Recent content in Wardley Maps on Open Security Summit</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/_template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/_template/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Events example and security implications of the isolation and terrorism</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/events-examples/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/events-examples/</guid><description>About this talk:</description></item><item><title>How do I do it - Bring your own map</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/how-do-i-do-it-byom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/how-do-i-do-it-byom/</guid><description>About this talk: After attending this useful session, you will be able to to create your own map by:
* Identifying your **users**. * Identifying your users' **needs**. * Adding the **capabilities** needed to successfully meet those needs. * Determining the stage of **evolution** for each capability by evaluating its characteristics. * Drawing the the complete **value chain**. * And finally getting your own **Wardley Map**! You will also explore the capability types, evolutionary characteristics and get even more useful information.</description></item><item><title>Keynote - Wardley Mapping</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/keynote/wardley-maps-keynote/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/keynote/wardley-maps-keynote/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Landscape and trends assessment</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/landscape-and-trends-assessment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/landscape-and-trends-assessment/</guid><description>About this talk: A map of a competitive business Landscape (a Wardley map) is visual and context-specific where the anchor is the User being served and their corresponding needs. The map contains a value chain — capabilities necessary to fulfill the needs, arranged according to their dependency relationships.
By attending this sessions, you will learn more details on the landscape and corresponding trends assessment, the position of the capabilities on the Wardley map and more information related to the topic.</description></item><item><title>Mapping culture</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/mapping-culture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/mapping-culture/</guid><description>About this talk: Wardley Mapping is a straight-forward process, and most difficulties boil down to concerns about making “mistakes” or doing the “wrong” thing. It is much more valuable to discard these concerns up-front, embrace the messiness of the process, and learn by boldly doing. The process of mapping is also the process of constructing a model of reality. An incorrect model that is also useful is the definition of success.</description></item><item><title>Risk Mapping - Applying Risk overlay with maps and security decision making</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/risk-overlay-with-maps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/risk-overlay-with-maps/</guid><description>About this talk: The more data penetrates into various industries, the more security threats and risks appear and it becomes really essential to deal with those risks and make the most optimal decisions.
In this session we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss how Wardley maps can be applied to improve the decision making process.</description></item><item><title>Security implications of the isolation and terrorism</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/security-implications-isolation-and-terrorism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/security-implications-isolation-and-terrorism/</guid><description>About this talk: We live in an age where data has penetrated into all areas of our lives, where everything gets captured digitally. Data helps companies and businesses grow, expand and improve their products and services, constantly apply innovations, better serve their customers and gain new ones.
While more and more companies gather data and share, store and access various files, it becomes vital to analyze files, prevent or spot unknown threats and struggle with malicious content, successfully manage incidents.</description></item><item><title>Strategy Development - applying the concepts (Wardley Maps)</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/strategy-development-applying-the-concepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/strategy-development-applying-the-concepts/</guid><description>About this talk: In this talk we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss 4 Problems for Cyber Security for the next Decade using Doctrine and Climatic patterns as the basis to discuss and develop potential solutions for it.
The Communications problem The Management problem The Engineering problem The Skills and Structure problem We will then break out into groups, to continue discussion on these and/or other problems and use Climatic Patterns and Doctrine to discuss and propose solutions for them.</description></item><item><title>Team Topologies &amp; PSD &amp; Squads &amp; Tribes</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/team-topologies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/team-topologies/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Threat Mapping (using Maps in Cyber Security)</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/threat-mapping/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/threat-mapping/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Wardley Mapping - content from last Summit</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/content/sessions-last-summit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/content/sessions-last-summit/</guid><description>Sessions focusing on the use of Wardley Maps in Security.
Following his participation in the 2018 Summit, Simon Wardley will be back :)
Wardley maps videos from 2018 Summit Wardley maps - part 1 of 2 Wardley maps - part 2 of 2 Presentations from 2018 Summit 2018 Outcomes: Create Wardley Maps for multiple security scenarios How how different groups mapped “Making Tea” and “AWS Attack” scenarios</description></item><item><title>Wardley Mapping resources</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/content/wardley-maps-resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/content/wardley-maps-resources/</guid><description>Atlas 2 - https://atlas2.wardleymaps.com/ You can login with a Google account or create one, and start mapping right away. It&amp;rsquo;s not feature rich, but a great and quick way to start
Creating Context-specific maturity models with Wardley Maps informed by Cynefin - https://medium.com/@chrisvmcd/mapping-maturity-create-context-specific-maturity-models-with-wardley-maps-informed-by-cynefin-37ffcd1d315 Lays out a process using &amp;ldquo;Building the right thing&amp;rdquo;, &amp;lsquo;Building the thing right&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Building the thing fast enough&amp;rdquo; and analyse options for investment using the Cynefin to make sense of the available options</description></item><item><title>Wardley Maps Introduction by Simon Wardley</title><link>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/wardley-maps-introduction-by-simon-wardley/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-security-summit.org/tracks/wardley-maps/working-sessions/wardley-maps-introduction-by-simon-wardley/</guid><description>About this talk: Wardley Mapping is a tool for strategic intent that supports you in your role as a knower, communicator, and a leader. It&amp;rsquo;s is a map of the structure of a business or service, mapping the components needed to serve the customer or the user. Wardley maps are named after Simon Wardley who created them in 2005. By attending this session, you will have an exceptional chance to get some basic knowledge on Wardley mapping, learn about its main pillars, get ideas for its practical usage and explore your most important questions directly with Simon Wardley and other participants.</description></item></channel></rss>